{
    "subject": "resource/Murata_Manufacturing",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Companies_listed_on_the_Osaka_Securities_Exchange",
    "human_readable": "Murata Manufacturing is about Companies listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9878199100494385,
            "question": "Is Murata Manufacturing listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.977860689163208,
            "question": "How does being listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange benefit a company like Murata Manufacturing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9446908235549927,
            "question": "Name some companies listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8399511575698853,
            "question": "Are there any other companies similar to Murata Manufacturing listed on the exchange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8059149384498596,
            "question": "Where is Murata Manufacturing listed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7962797284126282,
            "question": "What type of company is Murata Manufacturing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7842588424682617,
            "question": "What are some key characteristics of companies listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7673980593681335,
            "question": "What industries are commonly represented on the Osaka Securities Exchange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5656800866127014,
            "question": "What is the Osaka Securities Exchange known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48029953241348267,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about the history of the Osaka Securities Exchange?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Murata Manufacturing is about Companies listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1258_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the Osaka Securities Exchange known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1258_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industries are commonly represented on the Osaka Securities Exchange?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1258_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key characteristics of companies listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1258_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1258_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe documents do not mention anything about Murata Manufacturing being listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange. In fact, one of the documents mentions that the company was incorporated in Japan and is listed on the Tokyo Stock Exchange (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1258/re-ranker-msmarco/68.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information suggesting that Murata Manufacturing Co., Ltd. is listed on the Osaka Securities Exchange. Instead, the documents mention that it is listed on the Tokyo Stock Exchange."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}